<resources>
    <string name="app_name">first_app</string>
    <string name="para">here in the embryo does the person reside?
        Morphogenesis – the formation of the body from an embryo –
        once seemed so mystifying that scholars presumed the body
        must somehow already exist in tiny form at conception.
        In the 17th century, the Dutch microscopist Nicolaas Hartsoeker
        illustrated this ‘preformationist’ theory by drawing a foetal
        omunculus tucked into the head of a sperm.

This idea finds modern expression in the notion that the body plan is
        encoded in our DNA. But the more we come to understand how cel
        ls produce shape and form, the more inadequate the idea of a g
        enomic blueprint looks, too. What cells follow is not a bluepr
        int; if they can be considered programmed at all, it’s not wit
        h a plan of what to make, but with a set of rules to guide con
        struction. One implication is that humans and other complex or
        ganisms are not the unique result of cells’ behaviour, but onl
        y one of many possible outcomes.

This view of the cell as a contingent, constructional entity challenge
        s our traditional idea of what a body is, and what it can be.
        It also opens up some remarkable and even disconcerting possib
        ilities about the prospects of redirecting biology into new sh
        apes and structures. Life suddenly seems more plastic and amen
        able to being reconfigured by design. Understanding the contin
        gency and malleability of multicellular form also connects us
        to our deep evolutionary past, when single-celled organisms fi
        rst discovered the potential benefits of becoming multicellula
        r. ‘The cell may be the focus of evolution, more than genes or
        even than the organism,’ says Iñaki Ruiz-Trillo of the Institu
        te of Evolutionary Biology in Barcelona. Far from the pinnacle
        of the tree of life, humans become just one of the many things
        our cells are capable of doing.</string>
    <string name="from_android">From Android</string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">EXAMPLE</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">This is an app widget description</string>
</resources>